<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshop Setup on AWS Container DevSecOps</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/setup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workshop Setup on AWS Container DevSecOps</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="//localhost:1313/setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>AWS Cloud9</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/setup/cloud9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/setup/cloud9/</guid>
      <description>A list of supported browsers for AWS Cloud9 is found here.
   Launch Cloud9 in your closest region
Create a Cloud9 Environment: https://us-west-2.console.aws.amazon.com/cloud9/home?region=us-west-2
You&amp;rsquo;ll be prompt to log into your AWS Account in order to provision a Cloud9 Workspace
  Configure the Cloud9 instance  Review the setup before submitting for creation  Wait for the Cloud9 instance to boot  Increase disk size for your Cloud9 Instance  Increase the disk size of your instances, this will cause your instance to reboot</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud 9 Settings Configuration</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/setup/iam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/setup/iam/</guid>
      <description>Create IAM Role   Log into your AWS Account you are using for this workshop.
  Follow this link to create an IAM role with Administrator access.
  Confirm that AWS service and EC2 are selected, then click Next: Permissions to view permissions.   Confirm that AdministratorAccess is checked, then click Next: Tags to assign tags.   Take the defaults, and click Next: Review to review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop tools</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/setup/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//localhost:1313/setup/tools/</guid>
      <description>In order for us to continue with the exercises, there are several tools that our needed to be installed on our Cloud9 instance.
Download these two repos with git
git clone https://github.com/strongjz/devsecopspipeline
git clone https://github.com/strongjz/aws-container-devsecops
Or Download the script here.
  Scripts   tools-install.sh  (1 kb)    The script will install
 docker kind terraform eksctl kubectl helm  Navigate to where you downloaded the installation script.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
